#### **Oz Cohen Abramson**

# Full Stack Developer

odentionofficial@gmail.com | +972-54-7002414 | Github | LinkedIn | Portfolio

#### **Professional Summary**

I am a passionate Full Stack Developer, graduated from Israel Tech Challenge coding bootcamp.

During my time as a developer, I gained hands-on experience in developing complex applications using a range of programming languages and frameworks, including React, Node.js, Docker, Python, AWS, DigitalOcean and SQL/NoSQL databases. As part of a team-based curriculum, I collaborated with other developers on a variety of projects.

#### **Technical Skills**

Backend: NodeJS, Express , NestJS , SQL, MongoDB, Firebase, Heroku.

Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.

Other relevant skills: Python, Testing, Git, Redux, Docker, DigitalOcean, log systems, AWS, Micro-frontends.

#### **Work Experience**

### 2022 - present Full Stack Engineer, Synamedia

- Providing businesses with anti-piracy platforms (IPTV, OpenWeb).
- Building frontend Dashboards in React.js. handling both feature developments and whole projects architecture.
- Working with both Express and Nest as backend servers. Building both servers (nest and express) and microservices.
- Other tools: Docker, DigitalOcean, AWS, Github actions, Logs systems, tests, Python microservices.

### 2021 - present Lecturer, Israel Tech Challenge

- Introducing the world of Python to Cyber Security and Data Analyst students.
- Teaching the fundamentals of frontend development in Full-stack programs (HTML, CSS and JS Basics).

# 2021 Full Stack Developer, Fitback

- Developing a real-time workout feedback application for tracking user movements and exercise.
- Backend in Flask, connecting to the server for video analysis and MongoDB as a database.
- Frontend in React.js and redux, handling private routes for users and Machine Learning for feedback during workout.

#### **Education**

### 2021 Full-stack Coding Bootcamp, Israel Tech Challenge (ITC)

A 3-month full-time intensive training bootcamp focused on web development, using the latest languages and frameworks followed by a 2-month project in a high-tech company.

#### 2017-2018 M.A. Science & Philosophy, Bar Ilan University, Ramat Gan

Qualitative research course, academic research, analysis of daily electronic devices, mathematics aspects in Halacha.

# 2013-2017 **B.Ed. Natural Sciences**, Herzog College of Education, Jerusalem

Advanced computer applications course, statistics for science, Space Sciences course in Moscow.

# **Military Service**

2014-2015 Combat soldier, Staff Sergeant, squad commander and armored vehicle driver in Givati.

#### **Additional Information**

Languages:

Hebrew - native English - fluent.

• Interests:

Musician - Guitar, Drums, Bass

Freestyle frisbee

Japanese - Learning the language via Duolingo and iTalki